[Applause]
Yuko, thank you for your hard work at the Sync Club.
Thank you for your hard work.
From here, we are going to do rain treatment.
Yuko will be here after this,
So she's coming?
Summer.
Not yet.
Summer is already here,
I would like to deliver it with the four of us.
One more time, please.
Are you free tonight?
Would you go out with me?
I've always wanted to talk to you, Yucatama.
The rain.
Even if the rain stops, we'll still have a chatting party.
Ready, set, go!
Ame is for talking, and Ame is for chatting.
I'm Ame-chan for short.
YouTube Live! Ame Flash!
Good evening to everyone watching Fishers Channel.
Good evening. We are AmeFlash.
Yes, that's right, tonight we are starting with the three federations,
I'm in charge of the title call this time.
What was your seat?
No, I thought it was a mistake.
It was the most boring one.
Okay, here we go. This is Yukatama.
We almost ended up talking about the Taiwanese costumes and food.
She says I'm too cute and too serious.
Thank you very much.
The compliment.
I'm going to talk about Taiwan again today, but I think it will almost end up talking about food.
That's right.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
This is the part of the title call I've always wanted to talk to Marumaru about,
I will choose one person from those who tweeted their thoughts on Ameshabe,
We will call that person's name.
Please post a lot with the hashtag Ameshabe.
Please do.Please do.
Yes, by the way, isn't there something you really wanted to tell me about Haga?
Yes, there is.
That story, right?
It's like a dream, isn't it?
It's a story that Haga would never have told me if he won.
But even we can't give you a serious story.
Thank you. You think so?
I'm glad.
We talked together.
Just the day before, Haga received some surprising news that he never expected to win.
It's a big news about that thing that Haga likes and loves so much.
It's really true. It's really an unexpected thing. Like a dream.
Yes, it's true.
Haga...
We won't be able to eat that suger type we love on the Shinkansen anymore.
Oh no!
I want to eat it.
No, I don't. I don't think so.
Why not?
You were chewing on it.
I want some.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's true, but it's definitely not true.
That's true even if you don't want to eat it like this.
This is the reason why the bus sales on the Tokaido Shinkansen will end at the end of October.
I really can't.
We were really looking forward to it even after our life, so how could it be such an unexpected story?
That's not it.
Haga should say something about this.
It's impossible. What are you going to do?
What do you want me to do with the goal?
No, no, no.
We talk about it all the time.
I've been looking forward to it.
I knew it, but that's not how this conversation is going to go.
No, no, no. It's not.No, no, no. That's not true.
We talk all the time.
You know?
No way.
The Shinkansen wagons are going away.
What do you say?
Kendo? Kendo.
You're doing it, aren't you?
I'm not going to recommend any more, Haga-chan.
It's already different.
I'm talking to you.
She's just a baby. She's just a baby.
Yes.
My son's 3rd person is amazing.
That's right.
She made her dream come true.
Haga Kojima. Yes, I did.
I've appeared on ONE PIECE's official YouTube, Nakanagai's YouTube.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Because there's an episode.
They'll know, won't they?
I almost forgot.
I'm sure you all watched it,
I used to watch it a lot, and I'm sure they will come to my house next year.
NakanagaiThey are going to broadcast it on YouTube.
I will definitely be at my house next year.
And when they offered me a job, I was so surprised,
I was so surprised.
There was no way I would have my face on the screen next year.
I was really nervous.
My hands were shaking so much when I was doing the manma.
If it was on film, I'd be shaking.
It was amazing. When they say what I like, I talk really fast,
He speaks really fast and doesn't chew once.
He doesn't chew once.
Not a single bite.
I wish you'd keep it up all the time.
I'm talking to you.I'm talking to you.
I've been grinning a lot lately,
I've been grinning a lot lately, and the stories I've been telling about the special projects I've been working on,
I get so excited when I tell a story.
I grin all the time.
I've been doing that in the dressing room for a while.
All the time.
It was fun. And it was quite late at night,
I had to leave the place early,
He was very confessional,
I said I'd definitely go with Hana,
How long can you find that ONE PIECE story?
It's about 10 minutes too late.
It's been 10 minutes.
You still want to go home, don't you? Hana's been waiting.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I don't know what I'm doing. I thought I was going to win.
I was happy.
I was happy,
We talked a lot about ONE PIECE,
Kochi-san and Sukesan were very kind to me,
But it wasn't just that I knew so much about it.
Compared to Mr. Kochi and Mr. Sukesan.
But they talked to us a lot,
But there were still some things I didn't have enough to say,
I was going to talk about it,
I was going to say something, but I couldn't. I regretted it so much afterwards,
I regretted it a lot afterwards,
But I did.
But did you convey your love?
Yes, I did. Yes, I did.
I am glad.
Did Higashi Sensei hear me too?
Are you watching me, Azuma Sensei?
He's checking.
He's looking at the one I made too.
Together.
Now you can quit anytime you want.
No, it's not.
I have my dream cough.
My biggest dream is,My biggest dream is,
Ramping.
It's a long, long time.
It's a long time.
Let me say it now.
I'll work with you.
Really.
So here you go. Ladies and gentlemen, I'm Izuki Ikko.
This is Ikko Izuki.
Thank you for your hard work.
So, everyone,
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I've been waiting for you.
Sweets and cheesecake.
I want cheesecake.
I want to eat it.
I'll have some.
Here are sweets for everyone.
Ta-da!
No, that's enough.
I've been trying to tell you to stay in one piece, but you're so weak.
What dream?
My dream.
That's why.
That's enough.
What?
The one-piece dress with the candy floss.
I want to hear the "S" in "Shake One Mark".
You want to hear it?
It's rare.
I never listen to it.
You've never heard of it.
Shake One Mark's.
But today.
It's the summer special No. 6, so you want to hear it.
I want to hear it.
More than usual because it's the number 6 special.
I thought that if I talked about my dream, people would lose interest.
I thought.I was just thinking.
Do you have any idea how many times we've heard that?
We've heard it.
Today, of course, I'm working with Mr. Ikegawa as usual.
But today, we are doing Monday's session.
We are guests.
I mean, we are guests.
We are very much looking forward to doing this.
It was our first time at the SEEKER Club.
I couldn't meet them because I was on the other call.
But we were able to meet Linati and others.
Also, a lot of guests came.
It was a full house.
Thank you very much.
Now to the main topic.
Okay, let's continue.
I'd like to hear more details.
What kind of planning did you do?
Thanks for your time.
What kind of project did you do?
This is really good.
Please don't take it away from me. I'm talking to you.
I absolutely love this.
Okay, I'm going to be honest with you guys.
We are Abu Shabu tonight.
It's pre-recorded.
I don't know why I'm saying thank you, Yuzu.
I'm just saying.
You're saying it.
That's why we're doing it to accommodate Yuzu's schedule.
Here you go.
You've got to be kidding me. It's just me and Yuzu.
Because the three of us can't do anything together.
I'm going out of my way to be a bad judge of character.
Huh? Look at that.
You made me sleep so hard this morning.
You still overslept? See here.
It's still mid-morning.
I made it in time for the week, though.
I had to ring in the heat of the day.
You've got to be kidding me.You've got to be kidding me.
If Yuzu hadn't given me a cab ride, I would have been late.
You gotta be kidding me.
Yeah.
It was hot.
Then they decided the three of us couldn't do it.
That's not true.
If you do Abu Shabu over here, too.
If you do Abu Shabu over here, a lot of people will stop coming to watch the show.
That's right.
Because the government all-up caused it.
Because.
At the timing when the government all up is over.
Tell Mr. Tememan for about 30 minutes.
When did it end? When did it end?
I can't go into detail and check with him.
I can't check it with him.
It takes time for the staff to click when it's done.
I'm not getting it. Conclusion.
It's not coming out.
So I'm sure you all have sent your spotties to me.
I'm sorry. I can't read your name today.
I'm sorry, but I can't read your names today.
All of them are other than mine.
I'm the only three students.
Okay, everyone. Se-no.
Seriously.
Why not?
I'm sorry.
When you open the basket, a woman comes out.
A person comes out.
Ami, when you talk and open the basket, a woman comes out.
We three can't do it, can we?
We can't do it with just the three of us.
We can't do it without guests.
Thank you very much.
Anyway, I want to thank and apologize to the Spochaclass.
Thank you and apologize.
I apologize.
I made a mistake.I made a mistake.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, but I can't read your name.
I thought the person who had sent it to me could read it, so I sent it.
That's for sure.
I'll go first.
Thank you for sending me so many spotties.
Thank you very much.
I heard that you became a flower pusher for the first time today.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward to seeing you.
Please come and see us at the show.
Yes, thank you so much for sending me the spotlight.
Thank you very much. But today is a natural recording.
I can't read it out loud.
But I would like to read it out in my mind in the archive.
I would like to read it out from my heart in the archives.
I'm sure it's true.
Thank you for everything.
Yes, you sent me a spotcha.
Thank you all.
You said Moe Kan-chan is cute today.
I was very happy with your comments.
Thank you very much.
I'm here.
By the way...
Aida-chan's comment
I would like to have it.
I let you know when I saw Hana-chan for the first time.
I recommend Aida-chan.
I want Aida-chan to comment.
You've got to be kidding me.
We ate bread together today.
Maybe not.
Super.
Wait a minute.
Yours is the most visible.
How's the snacks?
I'm really sorry.
It's really Mr. Advertising's fault.
What do you mean?
I scanned the yuzu.If you scan Yuzu.
I think you'll be happy to know that Yuzu is on Misha Misha itself.
I have to send it from now on.
If Yuzu is there, let's send spacha!
Can you send Yuzu to me?
I don't know.
If you send it to me via spacha...
And if you send me to Spacha...
Go back to Misha Misha.
This is starting.
Then you can ask for spacha for everything if you want to code around.
You have to have spacha.
So much for not having people.
So much so that they comment on the code to go around.
I will do it with spacha.
As for me, I appreciate it.
Actually, you know, this Monday night.
I'm looking forward to answering what happens at the right time with the support.
Yes, I am. I'm looking forward to it.
That kind of video is fine.
I would like to bring you another one today with all four of us.
Please do.
So, so, continuing from last week, Mr. Suzuki.
Mr. Suzuki, this corner.
President Sononaka, please.
Yo!
Sunanbai!
LOL!
I'm sorry.
You know why I'm laughing?
Why?
Because I was different from one of the moekatake today.
No, no, no.
There's something different.
What?
Everyone looks different today.
Like the clothes.
We all have a dress code in common.We all have a dress code in common.
Wow!
Moe katake different things.
Some of them didn't bring that dress code.
Eh!
Oh, no.
We'll tell you the dress code?
Seino! Arline's clothes!
Random.
No.
The clothes I got from the heart.
I definitely don't know how he's saying it now.
I'm saying.
I am this today.
I'm being bullied.
Aryn-like.
I am to Arline.
I don't have any sweatshirts.
He asked me to give it to him when I don't need it anymore.
Sweatshirt top and bottom.
It's cute.
I have this
I'll have this shirt that is smooth and silky.
I'll take it.
I guess it's the season from here to here.
Why is it so silky?
Was it Osaka?
That's right.
The other day at the lesson.
Arline's clothes.
Chinese bag?
IKEA bag.
Plastic bags.
A glove bag.
Bags that look like storage.
About six.
Six bags?
Yes.
We're going to start the prima donna for free.
Tell them to take whatever they want.Tell them to go get whatever they want.
Bags for everyone.
They also bought bags for everyone.
that they could take home with them.
In the middle of it all
You can take as many as you want.
I'm going to put it in as soon as I win.
It's so great!
You mean they're taking more?
We couldn't fit them all in that box.
I wonder how many kilos they had.
When I came back...
I was on the train.
I had to cut so much off.
Will you put it in the box when you come back?
Yes, I will.
I didn't get in all the way.
That's nice. You're so sweet.
It's your first time, right?
Like summer clothes.
I had no clothes. I had to buy some.
About 10 to 20 clothes.
You don't have to buy.
About that.
So you smell like Arin?
Yes, it does!
It smells so much like Aline.
Didn't you wash it?
It would be a waste if I washed it.
I like the fabric softener.
It's Aline.
You can't tell.
Even if you buy it, you'll know it's Aline.
It's Aline.
I'm so happy.
You know, the clothes that Aline gave me.
It's not always the case, but sometimes it's great.
Don't ask me that.
I don't.
I don't look at the LINE all the time.I don't always look at the line.
That's right.
I haven't been getting LINE.
I've been on Instagram lately.
In the story section of my Instagram.
You know that thing on your insta-story that makes you feel like...
What's that?
It's a conversation between the three of us.
Oh, my God!
What is that?
You know what?
Once a day on the DMs.
Is it a new tweet?
A while ago. I think it's been a while.
So it's great.
But it's also mutual.
You like each other?
That part...
That's why I can only see it in idols and members.
You can only see it in the members.
You can't see that.
We are having a good time talking about idols.
Tell me about it.
It's very interesting.
I've always been in love with flowers.
Hana was originally into it.
Hana only follows these four people.
When Hana does it...
I won't be able to see it for a day or so.
It disappears for a day or so.
It disappears for 24 hours.
That's why I only follow these 4 people,
So, you know, leave her alone.
Because only everyone can see them.
Some of them are stardust.
I can see all of them.
So I made it just flowers with just my close friends.
So, I'm going to go in here.
Ira came in.Ira came in.
I thought, "Oh man, that's so funny.
I was at my best friend Ira's house, and Flowers came in one more time.
Why? Look at me.
Because she wouldn't come in.
I'm just saying...
Why don't you just let them in?
All of you.
You know, we're pretty physical,
It was fun.
Why?
How do you get the right answer when you read it?
The screen knows better.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know.
No, but..,
If you had told me when I was on the diet.
It's background music.
BGM after you're on a diet.
Why do you say that?
It's funny.
That's nice.
For example.
Yakiniku dishes.
Yakiniku
All you can eat at Yakiniku
Set the background music together.
Why can't you find it?
Haven't you seen the flowers?
We set it to Menick, didn't we?
But Ira's music is on.
The flowers are showing up.
Did they disappear?
That's exactly why you didn't do the bolo.
Ira's on day two.
Ira set the barbecue for the second day.
And on the second day, they disappeared.
I didn't know that.
I don't know, I tend to not know if it's an encounter or not.
I knew that kind of place.
I found a pause.I found a pause.
Found a pause?
Is he in?
You didn't tell me?
I told her I was.
He said he was doing it.
I have to find out.
He said he was going to meet someone.
I don't know.
But when I see everyone at the meeting...
I'm touching them.
I'm looking at them.
But I've never seen anything but Ira's.
I never hear anything like that.
I'm pretty sure it's just once.
I see it every day.
You watch it every day.
That's fine.
You don't have any memories of the two of them.
On the contrary.
Like Newton.
Even eight people.
Eight people.
We only saw the great parts.
I didn't see much.
It would be strange if we didn't see each other.
Someday, when I notice it...
We'll do it again.
I want the three of us to have fun together.
I hope you'll notice.
I saw a lot.
I'll watch it once.
Let's do it when you forget.
Yeah, let's do it when we forget about it.
We have such a dress code today.
but...
Was it a separate step?
I told you everything.
That's it!
I went to the Taiwanese satellite last time.Last time I went to Taiwan
I told you about it.
Today I'm going to tell you about ours.
We ended up talking about the flat side of things.
that we didn't have a chance to talk at all.
One more day to go.
One more day at the hotel.
We'll talk about the hotel and we'll be done.
Can you complete it today?
I hope so. It's just 15 minutes or so.
I'll just put in a few announcements and stuff.
Let's go for it.
He says we have 20 minutes.
What are we going to do? Can we just talk about the hotel?
Yes, that's right.
Which pair did you get this time?
In the last three minutes.
Ready.
Gotcha.
Mr. Hirabe looked very good.
That's right.
It's a gapper.
Yuzu was very popular.
That's right.
From Aya.
Yuzu and Akara went to Thailand last time.
We were super compatible in the same hotel.
So, from Ayala.
If the staff hadn't decided this time
Yuzu said, "Let's be together this time too.
We were talking about it.
Then, Mayaka and Hana said
all three of us like to take a bath in the morning.
Yuzu likes to take a bath at night.
If we bathe in the morning, we have to cut our bath time early.
I have to leave the bath early.
We eat.
Say that you want yuzu, too.
Hana would like that, too.If you say that, Hana...
She said she liked Yuzu.
Everyone liked Yuzu.
It's pretty early.
It's hard for me to wear it in the morning and at night.
It's pretty hard.
But it was.
That's why.
Moya Yuzu and Moya Yuzu were paired up
Paired with each other
Ayaka and Ayaka paired up.
I thought, "I have to go.
If it is an overseas satellite
I've never been to a hotel with an overseas satellite.
I've never been in a hotel.
I've never been to a hotel.
First time in Thailand.
Pair of two.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I'm paired with Hana.
I'm so happy to see how it will turn out.
The moment we get into the hotel, I'm going to be in bed with Hana, and we're going to be together.
Like a bed.
I was so happy to play with her on the bed.
I had a lot of fun playing with her.
That was fun.
Hana-ish.
You're so obvious.
Hanappo.
It's a little bit, you know, the children's team.
Why?
Because it's fun to dive.
If you guys are with me...
Dive.
We'd all do it.
I won't do it.
Yu doesn't do it.
But we will,
We'll be the first to climb up to the top.
To climb up to the top of other people's pechers.
There are people like that.Yes, there are people like that.
That's right.
You're just a kid trying to get back at them.
You're both kids.
It's like that.
Climbed up, climbed up, climbed up.
It's a little different.
The moment the game starts, the first thing to do is to decide whether to go with shoes or snippers.
or go with snippers.
That's how it started.
You know...
Stop it. It's like a fight.
Don't fight at all.
We're both a little...
We both have our own precious sides.
I have my own lump.
Yes, we do. If anything, there is a crassness and a precious side.
As a Kamite team, too.
Yes.
In the end, I'm going to snipper
My own.
I got two of them.
snippers and go in with them.
doing all kinds of things.
I'm an adult now, I'm an adult.
I kind of hate the range of shoe fits.
I see.
I don't allow it.
There's a bit of a difference.
But those snippers were quite a bit of fun, too.
You had this pair on the first day, right?
On the second day...
That's right.
I thought Yuzu was a popular guy.
But Mr. Suzuki...
I'm not?
I want to change.
No, I don't.
One more time.
What do you think?Well, what do you think?
Well, I don't know.
They don't really know what's going on.
I don't know.
So, you two are going to sit in my room in the morning,
I don't know, it just came out of the blue,
What's going on?
They're fighting.
But in the evening.
In the evening.
They sleep late into the night, a little bit too late,
The two of them.
They're having a good time, and then it turns into a little bit of a fight the next day.
I'm scared, I'm running away.
I'm scared.
As per my friend, I'm done sleeping all the way down to my stomach.
Speaker Dale already,
Like, seriously, tongue in cheek.
Even if I go to bed early, I'll be up early the next day,
We can't both sleep.
I thought "gumpa" would look good on my stomach,
I listen to them all the time,
I listen to him for a long time, but then I listen to him with all my heart.
I'm talking about something I know a little bit about.
I listened,
I couldn't sleep,
After it was over, something else started,
It started again.
Just the two of us.
The next day.
But we both hear it already, me too.
I can't do it anymore. I can't sleep.
I can't do it tomorrow.
If this happens again tomorrow,
I'll die.
I'm going to die.
And after the phone call,
I was so excited to talk about it next.
I'll get excited about it before we talk about it.
I'll do it later.We'll do it later.
We'll get excited before we talk about it.
That kind of thing is good.
But we got so excited.
I said, "I can't sleep now, what should I do?
So we did this,
Like, "I'll change tomorrow.
He said it was fine with flowers.
No, I was,
Even though we were talking on the phone,
Hana can sleep normally.
I'm the type of person who can sleep without worrying,
If you graduate tomorrow.
They look really good together.
It looks great on you.
It's a cab,
Mr. Sasaki was waiting for a cab even though he had flowers.
I was waiting for him.
It was 3:00 p.m.
And then he came, out of the blue,
It was like, "Today is different.
Like, "The other one has changed today.
And then I saw the other one's face,
The other one is in the very center.
Well, at that time, it looked really good on me.
It looked really good on me.
So, yes, you know,
It was summer,
I didn't know anything about it,
I said, "Why?
It was the first time.
I won't tell you why.
It was very appropriate to say it for the first time.
I thought it was really scary.
Yeah, we looked at each other.
What? What are you going to say? What are you going to say?
I'm not thinking about anything.
I know.
That's what I thought,
But you're too serious.But it's too serious face.
So.
Because there are times when I'm at home,
Because I ended up doing so much variety until yesterday,
I'm wearing a circle.
I thought it would be that kind of picture.
I didn't get it, you know.
I'm doing variety.
You didn't feel anything? The circle.
There's another reason for this,
When you said you wanted to change rooms,
Yuko liked my skin, right?
She said something about my skin and how nice it was,
It's the most amicable way to end the relationship.
No, love is different.
I'm definitely polluting the world,
I feel like I can't come over here.
I see. I can bring it all together.
You mean you can put it all together.
I don't think so.
Judging from what's behind you.
That's right.
Ai-chan is going to organize, right?
That's right, much more of a camp.
So, Yuko made it into skin.
So you liked it on the skin.
But from my point of view,
I think she was having a lot of fun with it.
It's pretty good for the skin.
Almost a little bit of the camp.
Ai ga target.
Love is the target.
Love is the target. We were having fun.
You were a little bit in love,
It's a little bit fun.
A rose, yes.
You were in love.
I hear you're her type.
I like your type.
How much?How much?
I like this one better.
Hey.
I know you're the victim here.
But, you know, we talked about changing rooms,
Ai-chan didn't even tell anyone about it.
But I thought, you know,
We're in the same room,
But, as an example, I think we should go, too.
Are you okay, Ai?
Yes. You should go, love.
Love should go.
But it's okay.
Love was just having fun, you know?
Love was doing flowers and stuff.
Malaysia, you know, flowers and stuff,
The next Malaysia, uh, Malaysia.
In Taiwan, they were doing flowers, and the next Malaysia was already good.
I was looking forward to the order.
Then suddenly, the flowers were taken away.
They were taken away.
Mr. Suzuki, who was in the room with earphones in both ears, came in.
Wow, that was amazing. I was so surprised.
It was these two on the second day,
The next morning, during some kind of interlude,
Did you have a conversation? I said,
No, Moemika had her earphones in,
What did you talk about that night?
Yay.
So, MoMika, you know, she's nice, right?
Yeah, you know, she and Yuzu are together, you know.
Yuzu talks to me.
So we have fun.
And Hana does something for me.
Hana.
If something comes, you do flowers.
But they don't come, so I don't do flowers.
I didn't want him to talk to me.
Not at all.
I thought he wanted some time alone.I thought he wanted some time alone.
But I don't remember being a shutter nut, and there was no way I was going to fall.
But I don't think I did at first.
It was a little while after we moved,
Someone came in, and Moemika came in with earphones and said she was lonely.
But she didn't say anything.
He said it was an earphone.
Is it you directly or is it okay to worry?
I'm pretty rough around the edges when it comes to my lifestyle.
You're the type of person who cares.
You're the type to worry.
And then I became the type of person who wanted some time alone.
That's why I was so worried about you, and that's why you talked to me.
Oh, that's right.
He was wearing earphones and suddenly started watching YouTube or something,
He stopped talking to me in the middle of the conversation.
I thought about whether or not I would like it.
But you wear earphones, don't you?
I wear them in the dressing room, too.
But you say, "But, you know...".
But in fact, you're surprisingly talking to Yusato and Hana on your own.
Maybe he doesn't like them.
He must be getting to dislike them.
I might definitely come to Malaysia next time.
But he's playing music like that,
Boom-boom-boom.
Oh, I see.
I thought that was cute.
I felt like my head was wet even though I was wearing a towel.
It's like, "Beep, beep, beep.
They're dancing.
It's like I'm longing for a foreign movie.
It's so funny.
I wanted to take a picture of it, but I couldn't.
I didn't get a good amount of zoom down.
No matter, they looked like they were having fun.
In the morning.
Disney music all the way.
Voice coordination.
No, no. Why not? Wan wan wan wan.No, no. Why not? Wan wan wan wan.
You saw it.
It was pretty early in the morning.
Yes, it was.
I think that, uh, Yoshiyuu's room is the best.
I see.
But there were some complaints from the staff of the office that they asked you not to change the room without permission.
Yes, that's right. Let's not say so much.
What do you think?
The fire department also complained.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yeah, I guess so.
So, you were surprised when I didn't go to my room.
Really?
Yes, I was.
What? Which way did they go?
Well...
Does that happen?
Oh, yeah.
I'm here.
Ha-ha-ha.
Feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing a lot of things.
It's fun, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
After all, you know, Yuzu called his friends every day at Evul.
So, as a result of that, you call them?
That's right.
Oh, no. They kind of understand me.
We do it in the middle of the night.
I'm on the phone with a friend of Yuzu's.
What? You know them?
Ha-ha-ha.
Do you know?
I don't know.
So, um, Hana is friends with Yuzu's friend and they've been talking on the phone for about two hours.
Still?
With Yuzu's friend.
Ha-ha-ha.Ha ha.
That's right.
Yes, yes.
What a yoo-hoo.
I don't think he has anything to discuss with Kojima.
I know.
I thought you were going to do something very different.
Yeah, I see.
Okay, then.
But, you know, it's a concert with other people's friends.
It's a concert with other people's friends.
Right.
Let's do it.
Yuzu loved this kind of thing.
You loved it, right?
Yeah.
Congratulations.
I'm looking forward to the Malaysian version.
Come see me again.
Let's get you knitting.
Our knitting.
We'll just use their names eventually.
What grade are these two still in?
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
I only grew one day in a tie.
I only grew for a day
I only had it for one day.
I can say that a lot.
There's nothing I don't like about it, but...
I said something about "ayakan".
Yes, I did.
I don't want to say anything for a while.
That's a lie.
When Mr. Suzuki said it, I was surprised.
When Mr. Suzuki said it...
Mr. Suzuki...
Mr. Suzuki, that's it.
He cut off the slippers in his room, and they live together.
Ayanan's slippers were used a lot!I used Ayanan's slippers a lot
I used Ayanan's slippers a lot!
You're naked!
I have slippers.
What?
After the exchange.
Ayanan's two slippers were left behind.
I think she took them from her room.
I found about three in motion.
The type near the front
The type close to the front
This is Bite Art's demonstration method
Bite Art
I thought I had it earlier.
Yes, sir.
Hotel like this
The hotel was a lot more fun than I thought it would be.
We had a great time at the hotel.
I'm going running on the last day.
I see.
10 minutes
Last day.
Night 1
I went
It was already a sightseeing-on-duty day.
It was a sightseeing-on-day day.
He made such a schedule for us.
I went there.
I had free time.
It was pretty much a full day.
It was the schedule of the title.
It was very fulfilling.
We set up a swag.
We had a bus and everything.
That's the lantern I gave you, right?
That's right.
Make a wish.
Different colors.
There's a different wish for each color.
I'd give it to you if I saw it on your Instagram.I'd give it to you if I saw it on Instagram.
This is the pink and
These are the member's colors.
who?
Pink purple
Pink Blanca
Red
Blue
Yellow
Yellow, pink, light blue
Yellow makes sense.
I'll tell you.
Yellow is vigorous.
Yellow means good luck
Blue for good luck in work and business
Pink is for more happiness than happiness
And red is for good health.
of health.
So, they're all good for each other?
Don't you love money?
Here's the money.
If you want to move your position.
All of them, one for each of you.
Actually, you know, the light pink and the dark pink.
I wanted to do dark pink.
Relationships will be irresistible.
Wow!
So, you know, you'll have so many more guesses.
That's for sure.
At this point in my life, I've even been with people who are popular.
I've been thinking I want this so bad.
Well, but I've got a pretty good idea of what I'm going to do.
I even tried to do a dark pink-only one.
I want to be popular! You know...
I've got a lot more fans.
How many can I give you?
Just one.
I think that's a good idea.
I don't want it to be too much of an effort.
But, you know, there was one that had all the colors.
Wow! That's amazing!Wow! That's amazing!
He helps me so much when I fly.
He strokes it so much!
He's posing for me to see.
Pee!
Hello!
Rich Manny!
He's petting her so much.
He takes videos and everything.
But when I drew them randomly...
The individuality of the land was amazing.
It had a different personality.
I guess so.
But they're all pretty much the same.
The gold part.
It says "don't waste your money.
I wonder if that's true.
That's what I meant.
I'm a financial guy.
I don't go into debt.
LOL.
Vanguard.
I hope it's raining happy money.
This time.
I think it fell randomly around there.
It went up beautifully.
It went down beautifully.
I liked it a lot.
And the food.
It was delicious.
It was like a stella. It was delicious.
We all ate.
The next volume is Ghibli
Cube.
Cube is called Ghibli.
Famous, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's that one... but the stairs were hard.
I really loved it that day.
It was hot.
We went from the bottom, so we had to climb all the way up the stairs.We went from the bottom, all the way up the stairs.
We all had to get to the top.
I'll try to get a picture.
I don't want a visual.
Let's go somewhere cool and chilled.
Go into the tea shop and go on.
You say beef bowl
Beef noodle soup
Yuzu went there with some friends.
It was super nice.
I recommend the watermelon. It's like a coffee shop.
There was this place.
50% of the people were there.
It was really good.
And the rice with takikomi gohan...
The one we had together looks delicious.
Like, um...
It's like alcohol.
It was absolutely delicious!
Did you have the food?
Just the two of us.
Yeah, I guess so.
Basically, everything was delicious.
It's delicious.
It's like Japan.
There are so many places.
It's called "Beef bowl".
It smells a little...
Like natto in Japan.
It smells like kismet.
At a food stand...
Yuzu.
Even if you're about 10 meters away.
I can smell the shudo.
I'll try to run
to the silver car.
It's got really good teeth.
I've known for quite a while.
You know how there's a straight left and a straight right?
If you turn left, I can smell it.If you turn left, you'll smell it.
There's definitely a monastery on the left, so I have to go.
I'll be at Tanaka's.
He asked me if I was really a shoe.
It really smells great.
It really smells like a monastery.
You know, the kind where you say, "I really can't.
It doesn't fit.
It's like a whoosh.
Sure, no problem.
It's pretty much nightly for me.
I know, right?
What's with the skin?
It's normal.
It's like a whoosh.
I feel sorry for you.
It's just normal.
I'm still fine.
It's hard.
Tough.
It stinks.
It's a skin thing, right?
I don't get it in my face that much.
I can smell it on myself.
I've been wanting to try it.
It doesn't taste very good.
Yeah, it's good, too.
It's good.
Next time someone should try it.
You really should try it.
You lose.
Whoever wins gets to try it.
OTOBUKI JUNKEN
Whoever wins gets it.
I'll eat so much lemon then.
After all this trouble
I'll eat lemon every day of the week
I'll eat it.
That's what I was going to do anyway.
Go for 10 minutes.
After thatAfter that
Vacation
Go on vacation.
You know, like Harajuku.
Like Harajuku.
Before that...
Sholon.
Sholon?
No, no... a massage.
That's it.
That's it, isn't it?
Sholon, like a shopping arcade.
You go to a place like Harajuku on the schedule.
Tell her she can go there for a massage.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
That's why I can't remember the massage.
Youth said they'd finish it up.
Three or four of us got massages.
You all went together?
We all went together.
Can someone give you a message?
Oh, they told me.
I don't know.
Uh...
Bell came out.
I forgot how much it hurts.
Someday it will never end
Oh, after a time
Yes, yes, yes
Yeah, yeah, yeah
It felt so good.
All over?
No, shoulders and feet.
Like a foot massage.
The course was just that...
The whole body was a little too long.
A little too much on the hands.
The next time I went, I was greeted with a warm welcome, despite the minute I arrived.
I was greeted warmly and
I felt so good!
He was very kind to the Japanese.He was kind to the Japanese.
What's that in Japanese?
Japanese.
It said Roppongi.
It's a restaurant in Roppongi.
At the Roppongi School.
I highly recommend it.
It was really, really good.
I went to Taiwan and they had a massage place called Roppongi.
They gave me a massage.
It's like Roppongi Marumaru.
It's easy to find.
It was so clean inside.
Super clean.
It's so clean!
It was great!
And it was super comfortable.
And I slept like a bomb!
I fell asleep right away.
He was sleeping right next to me.
You were?
I was sleeping next to you.
I fell right asleep.
I had a massage, but it was pretty bad.
And I've already read that yuuhu's on the building line.
I read that it's a good night's sleep.
I'd fall asleep on his shoulder and the one next to him.
My self-confidence was so bad.
I'm not so sure about myself.
Oh, that's right.
My shoulders were so bad.
The worst angle
Shoulders are like that
Yuhki says that she tries to make the angle as cute as possible
Yuhki tries to make it as cute as possible.
That's why she uses an angle app to take pictures.
Normal angle is the ugliest angle.
She used to sleep like this.
I'm on my shoulder here.
I'm not confident anymore.
It's more malicious this way.It's more malicious this way.
It's malicious.
It's not cool.
It was a super nice place.
I want to go back.
You're having a great time.
So, first we went to a restaurant?
Gastronomical restaurant? - Gastronomical restaurant.
Xiaolongbao!
That's the best!
Massage.
I'm starving.
Why can't we just go out for dinner?
It's like a Chinese restaurant.
It's delicious.
A basket of dumplings.
I kind of liked it.
The dumplings were delicious.
but the shrimp dumplings were also really good!
And the jarred noodles...
Jar Jar Noodles are also delicious!
And the cucumbers were delicious!
Eggplant was delicious!
It was good.
And I also ordered the sweet kind... the ones with the sweet stuff in the dough.
Moemi ordered food.
It was delicious!
Yuzu ordered kosian.
That was surprisingly good.
And the sweet stuff.
You ordered custard, right?
When was that?
When did you order that?
The food was really good.
The food, too.
I liked the food, too.
The kimchi was really good.
It was really good.
It was really good!It was really delicious!
I was so happy to be able to say "Thank you very much!
We ate a lot of delicious food!
After that, we went to Nishikasa-machi, which is said to be like Harajuku!
Yuzu
Oh, no, it's yuzu!
Yuzu also has intellectuals and managee.
I was just going at it.
Yuzu is Poca Paula in a bottle.
The last time I was there with my friends, they were selling poka-pola in bottles.
It was a very cute miniature size.
It's so cute, isn't it?
That's what I wanted.
I was looking for it at the benefit, but they didn't have it.
That's right.
Then the yuzu ones.
At Managee.
As a product there.
Poca Paula in a bottle.
And it was a spray.
Minimal size.
All of them.
You mean tiny bottles?
Yeah.
Miniature bottles, like this one.
Super cute.
Yuzu did the manage to get it.
It went in.
You sprayed it on?
Yeah.
Like, you can have it.
All of us.
That's all we wanted.
We were all going back and forth.
I was wondering if you'd give me that bottle from there.
That's what I thought.
From the cardboard.
Out of the cardboard came a regular canning jar.I got a bottle of regular cans.
Eh!
All of us.
Oh, no!
Not that one?
Not the bottle?
That one.
I'm so excited.
So, you know.
I was walking.
I was walking again.
And I saw a managee shop in a different part of town.
I saw it was there.
I saw it was there again, in that little bin.
And I did it when I crossed over.
Three days ago...
It was on some kind of alcohol.
And they gave me the whole bottle.
That's right.
That's why you open it.
This mog bag is on it.
Cross over by the keri one more time.
It was the wrong mog bag.
So I said, "Yuzu, I can do it. I can do it.
I said, "I want to keep going.
but I'm worried about Yuzu, so I said, "Let me check just in case.
He said...
Excuse me.
If I buy this, can I have it?
Which one?
I said, "Which one?
I'm serious.
Aah!
I see.
Okay, okay.
Not at all.
I don't know.
I guess it's because we all want it.
It's a little counterintuitive.
Right?right?
That's why.
But that car-like thing...
If you break more than three balloons.
I wonder if it's some kind of punishment.
With Aya.
Aya and I were like, "This is definitely going to hurt!
And then we did it.
All of them.
So I had to guess 100 times out of 100 to get the balloon.
I can't get a balloon.
What?
You're gonna guess?
No, you didn't.
I had a 1 in 2 chance of winning.
That's right.
100 times out of 100.
That's a lot.
A lot.
About 20.
Twenty.
I'm trying not to make it.
What a surprise.
You must be a hot madam.
That's right.
I thought you didn't know the rules.
But I'm glad we had a good time.
It was fun.
Did you guys finish it?
Yatai. - Yatai.
Yes, we did.
I'm an American hula player.
I see all those post-finishing rules.
That's nice.
What about accessioning?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can beat Axter.
Mm-hmm.
No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And if we do that, we can get Ameetha.I'd like to do it every day.
I'd like to do it every day.
I'd love to.
They have regular fireworks shows in Tokyo.
You could do a candy fling there or something.
Good... study up.
"I'm an idol!
It's good. It's good.
Kon-chan, chocolate bananas.
And put on the Osakani outfit that Daichi gave you.
Keep it on.
It's like you'll never win.
I told him I'm an idol.
They were so surprised.
I said, "She's an idol.
It was like Osaka and Komatsu were going to appear every once in a while.
I said, "They're idols.
They said, "Let's say you're an idol.
If things had changed that much...
Very, very, very...
That's great.
It's true, she's an idol.
Like Joss the dog.
If you do that...
It's a good place in Taiwan.
You know...
It's a good place in Taiwan
Very, very, very...
You know how they used to follow me?
I really liked the license plate numbers over there.
They were so cute.
What do you mean?
Yuzu was having a discussion.
There were four boys and three girls behind them the whole time.
I mean, there was no eye contact at all.
There's four of them, right? They were staring.
And they were wearing these really cool wigs and stuff.
And they're like, "Hi.
And that's all we talked about.
And then after the school was over.When you're done learning in
We all turned to the back like this, to the right.
And just when I was starting to think there was no one there...
They were here to learn.
And I said, "Do you want to learn? They were so cute.
They were so cute.
Are they your friends?
And then they called me on my cell phone.
He was like, "What?
He was like, "Oh, my God!
He was so cute.
I thought he was younger than me.
She was so cute.
She's an easy girl.
I'm fine with the wig, Ira.
Just the wig.
Just a wig?
They say the wig will make you fall in love with Mr. Ira.
With a wig?
With a wig.
She said it made her feel hot to be a wig.
Don't do that if it makes you squeamish.
I also thought it would be nice if you said "nageage".
If you think it's cute, it's fine.
He's cute.
Why?
She said it made her feel hot.
Not yet.
For both of us.
No, I'm not.
I'm just not getting picked on by anything.
What?
Like going to a fancy restaurant for a full course meal.
Second time.
I'll go out with you.
I might do it a second time.
In a manner of speaking.
That's not good.
I'll give you some time.I got to spend a little time with you.
That was fun.
Super fun.
And that day...
And then there was that day.
I left in the morning.
I came home safe.
Of course.
But you know what?
The time before you left...
Right?
You're leaving?
I don't know.
Before you leave.
I didn't have two minutes, so I thought I'd give you three.
Well, I had a few minutes, so I thought I'd buy some souvenirs.
At the airport?
Yeah, I sold out.
And then we were like, well, let's make an appearance.
We only have 30 minutes.
We'll meet in front of that exit in 30 minutes.
Yes, sir.
So if we do the passport thing in about 30 minutes...
I thought that I could make it in time.
So I bought some souvenirs and ordered some pasta.
I ordered pasta and so on.
After we came in, the inspection was a big hit.
It was a big hit!
It took me 10 minutes to get there.
Penn! Penn!
It's over.
I think I'm done.
Let's do an inspection that we can't handle in 10 minutes.
Because after that, it's going to take a long time to get to the exit where it's going to appear.
I see.
That's right.
I can't get on. I can't go home.
I can't go home.
So, the inspection was over about 5 minutes ago.
And then, three minutes later, I was on my way to the exit.From 3 minutes to the exit of its appearance.
I already let him out.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, guys.
And you're on your own now.
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't do it, you can't do it.
And we were at home, too, at noon.
So I came home a little late
But we all did like sneakers
Me, lessons.
And I was like, "Oh, my God.
My boots were so heavy.
Ha-ha-ha.
They were too heavy.
My boots were so heavy
I really can't do it
I can't do it. I can't do it.
Beer was slower than me.
I was about the same size as Beale.
It's getting farther and farther away.
Ha-ha-ha.
And then you just leave it behind.
Somehow it all worked out.
We made it.
Another miracle.
When we were standing in line...
There were two in the studio.
And when I thought I couldn't make it to the middle of the line...
But somehow, the staff opened this rail.
They opened up this rail and added another rail.
And they added another rail.
It was just one row from our place.
the first row from our place.
It was amazing!
About two rooms behind us
They came through.
They closed it.
Again?
Yeah!
There were only about three couples there.There were only about three couples there.
So you only opened it for a moment?
Yes!
Shay shay shay!
They were saying, "Shay shay shay!
Really shake shake!
Really shake shake shake!
I'm pretty sure that happened about three times.
If it hadn't been for that, he would have definitely done it to the plane.
And then after that, something else.
He did it just now.
Super shay shay! Shay shay shay!
Really shay shay shay!
Main Actor
Shay shay shay! Shay shay shay!
Shay shay! Shay shay!
I'm glad you're back.
I'm glad you're home, but I didn't think you could make it.
I think he might still be here.
I still don't know what he was doing.
Maybe I still need to know.
It's the same as when I had to know.
Sprite Pimpin'! Oh, my God!
I don't know what I'm doing.
It's still cool.
But I'm glad you're home.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It's nice to be able to go abroad
I thought it was really fun
I thought it was really fun.
If anyone who came to this fan tour
If you are interested in joining Sanji
I said, "Come back again.
I said, "Come back again"? Something like that.
I said during the tour
I thought maybe five people would come.
And that's part of it.That's part of it.
I also took the Sanji exam.
A lot of people really wanted to meet
to meet Sanji.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm also looking forward to Malaysia.
I'm really looking forward to Malaysia too
People are looking forward to Malaysia!
How many are you going to say?
You forgot.
Wow.
I feel like I'm completely off the grid.
It's so obvious.
They're not going to cut it. They're going to record it.
No, they don't.
If you say it's off the hook, it's off the hook.
Oh, yeah.
What?
What kind of mannequin are you looking forward to when you see this Malaysia?
Mane, mane, mane.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What?
What? It's so lifelike.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, my God, my God, my God, my God, my life.
We could be dead.
I think I might be dead.
I have a stomach ache
I'm just getting carried away.
I'm getting carried away
I'm on a roll
My stomach hurts
It's mixed up.
It's a major cause of death.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's gonna get mixed up.
We're such a we, but still...We're like this, but we're not quite there yet
We have this kind of love, but
We still have summer and festivals coming up.
We also have Amman, so please look forward to it!
Please look forward to it!
So, I would like to make such an announcement.
Yes, sir.
I don't have the words for announcements.
There are many things, but the most important thing is
The most important thing is
December 22nd.
Shinagawa Spirago!
The most important thing!
It's very important.
This is our 5th anniversary!
November 3rd is our 5th anniversary.
It's our 5th anniversary, and this is our 5th anniversary live concert.
I'm going to talk about it in the Shinagawa Spirago.
I'm going to talk about it at Shinagawa Spirago.
It's a very large capacity.
I think it's the biggest among the members.
1000 capacity
1000 upper capacity
1000 upper capas.
We've never been filled to 1000 before.
I would like to invite you all to join us, Soul Doubt style.
That's our goal.
We want lots of people to come and see the show.
Please invite your friends and family.
Please come!
Tickets are now being accepted. Thank you very much.
Tickets are available until 11:59pm today.
until 23:59 today, so
I really look forward to seeing you all there!
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
You can still get a ticket on a specific day.
That's right.
Please get it!
I'll buy one for my friend, too.
Please go!
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, the customer is...
Yes, sir.
So, last but not least, of course, this corner!
Yes, Suicune again this week.
Applause
I've been waiting for you.
What's this week's Suicune
What is this week's rebuttal?
This week's Suicune.
Really?
This week's Suicune is playing with a toy that makes noises.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
It makes a squeaky sound.
It's amazingly cute.
Here we go.
I drove.
I'm a little concerned about something.
I'm worried about you.
Hanako-san and Hana-no-sis's voice
I can't help but be concerned.
That's not true.
I'm listening to the squeak.
I'm listening to the sound of toys.
He's so scared.
He's so freaked out.
Oh, my God.
Yes!
Next week, Hanako, too. That's not it. Let's say you're like Hanako.
Tenterette. That's right. I only think of my father as Tenteret.
And, um, sister. Amazing.
I wonder what she's doing. Even my dad reminds me of him.
Yes, I do. That was this week's Osuiken.
Well, it's time to say goodbye for this week. Lastly, I'd like to ask you to give us your best effort from Mark on the subject, Moya Moya Magic.
Yes, I will. A drop of Malaysia!
Oh yes, you must have had a drop, didn't you?
Clothes and hair are pale.
My wife's trigger is desperate. I don't feel like it.
I'm just trying to be careful 387 about my wife.387 minding your wife.
I'm definitely taking it off.
I'm gonna take it off... for a while.
Oh, I'll close my hand.
I'm going to lose my hand.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I'm so excited.
Oh, my God! Before you worry about that!
It goes on and on and on and on...
Thanks for the next content patch!
Bye-bye!
Come on, get mad.
That's not fair.